export const level2 = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "126 + 200",
      answer: ['301', '326', '289', '433'],
      true_ans: '326',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "400 / 25",
      answer: ['16', '18', '22', '15'],
      true_ans: '16',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "23 * 30",
      answer: ['560', '629', '690', '584'],
      true_ans: '690',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "478 - 256",
      answer: ['222', '135', '256', '189'],
      true_ans: '222',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "225 + 475",
      answer: ['660', '975', '700', '580'],
      true_ans: '700',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "550 / 11",
      answer: ['11', '25', '54', '50'],
      true_ans: '50',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "24 * 25",
      answer: ['530', '600', '540', '480'],
      true_ans: '600',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "486 + 243",
      answer: ['789', '549', '686', '729'],
      true_ans: '729',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "158 * 3",
      answer: ['474', '514', '486', '354'],
      true_ans: '474',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "2 * (2 + 5) - 4",
      answer: ['5', '8', '10', '15'],
      true_ans: '10',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "6 + 3 * 8 - 9",
      answer: ['63', '21', '3', '11'],
      true_ans: '21',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "25 * 25",
      answer: ['666', '525', '455', '625'],
      true_ans: '625',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "990 / 33",
      answer: ['33', '30', '28', '19'],
      true_ans: '30',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "642 + 287",
      answer: ['929', '889', '919', '899'],
      true_ans: '929',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "(12 + 8) / 4 + 24 * 5",
      answer: ['130', '98', '120', '125'],
      true_ans: '125',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "3 + 3 * 3 - 3",
      answer: ['9', '6', '12', '15'],
      true_ans: '9',
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: "56 * 3",
      answer: ['158', '174', '168', '200'],
      true_ans: '168',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "102 / 3",
      answer: ['34', '60', '72', '42'],
      true_ans: '34',
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "541 + 263",
      answer: ['794', '764', '854', '804'],
      true_ans: '804',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "766 - 60",
      answer: ['703', '696', '706', '721'],
      true_ans: '706',
    },
  ];
  